

CONTACT

mehtakhushi73@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/ khushi-mehta-b82b641b0/



+91 89553 80952



Jainam Ceramics, Udyambag, Belagavi, Karnataka, 590008

SKILLS

- · Content writing
- · Upselling and Cross selling
- Canva
- Oratory skills
- · Ability to work under pressure
- Interpersonal skills
- Patience
- Negotiation skills
- · Active listener and observer

HOBBIES

- · Active content consumer
- · Reading books
- · Listening to music
- Playing keyboard
- Gardening

LANGUAGES KNOWN

- English (Spoken) Fluent
- English (Written) Intermediate
- Hindi (Spoken) Intermediate
- Hindi (Written) Intermediate
- Marathi (Spoken) Beginner
- Kannada (Spoken) Beginner
- Kannada (Written) Beginner

SOCIAL



@_khushimehta___



@mehtakhushi18

KHUSHI MEHTA

ABOUT ME

I'm 22, born in Rajasthan, and brought up in Belagavi, Karnataka. I come from a family of four, my father is a businessman who teaches me to be a workaholic, my mother is a housewife from whom I learn multitasking, and my sister is a science student who makes me believe that having big dreams is important in life.

I'm a graduate with a Bachelor of Business Administration, academically specializing in the field of digital marketing. I believe in giving 100% to everything I do and have keen attention to detail.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Operations and Strategy Manager | Jainam Ceramics

April 2023 to Nov 2023

Dec 2022 to Feb 2023

- Transformed manual inventory management and billing system into digital, increasing 45% efficiency in operations
- Strategised plans for a new business venture of ceramic printing and handling competitive product analysis
- Designed a digital marketing approach of creating digital catalogues and listings on business platforms, increasing sales by 15% in combination with offline marketing and maintaining customer loyalty

Content Writing Intern | Grimbyte Technologies - Remote

- · Working on ideating content for their website
- Creating content purely on the entertainment genre
- Working on the back end of the website to post articles through WordPress
- Posting 3 articles per day including editing of those articles
- Conducting proper research via various social media platforms and other sources before posting any article.

Client Servicing Intern | Laudco Media Pvt. Ltd. - Bangalore

May 2022 to June 2022

- Worked on Client Solutions and Retention
- Serviced 10+ Clients in the span of one month (Flipkart, Truffles, Renee cosmetics)
- Worked on balancing internal and external communications
- Made media plans and commercials for performance and influencer marketing
- Lead Generation via strategic outreach on social media and networking platforms
- Content concept ideation and blog content creation
- Online and Offline Campaign execution

Digital Marketing Intern | CyclingZens Pvt. Ltd. - Goa

Oct 2021 to Nov 2021

- Worked on thoroughly understanding the business model of the company.
- Created B2B presentation, posters, and infographics, used various social media platforms like Instagram, Facebook Business suite, LinkedIn to schedule posts.
- Set up various digital platforms like Bokun, Airbnb, Tripadvisor, Linktree, Hootsuite
- Designed Instagram guide, calendar, reels and job postings on LinkedIn.
- Also worked on content standardization, and created new product catalog.
- Generated influencer leads

CERTIFICATIONS

- Principles of Leadership (Great Learning, 2023) | Process Management (Great Learning, 2023) | Project Management (Great Learning, 2023) | Asset Management (Great Learning, 2023) | Introduction to Corporate Finance (Great Learning, 2023) | Product Management (Great Learning, 2023) | Tally ERP-9 (Tally Solutions, 2020)
- Fundamentals of Digital Marketing Google Digital Garage, Sep 2021
- Supply Chain Management: A Learning Perspective Coursera, Nov 2020
- Effective Business Communication NPTEL (coordinating institute IIM-B)

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION

S. No.	Course	Name of the institution	Percentage	Year of passing
1.	Bachelor of Business Administration	KLE Society's College of Business Administration Lingaraj College Belagavi, Karnataka, India	96.55%	2019-22
2.	Pre-University College	Jain Heritage School, Belagavi, Karnataka, India	76%	2017-19
3.	SSLC	Amrita Vidyalayam School, Belagavi, Karnataka, India	95% (10 CGPA)	2016-17

POSITIONS OF RESPONSIBILTY

- As Team Lead, organized inter-collegiate fest, with 10 members.
- As Event Head, organized inter-school fest, with 20 members.
- School Head Girl in 11th Grade.
- School Captain in 10th grade.
- Cultural Secretary in Secondary School.

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Awarded a Gold Medal and an academic excellence award for consistent past performance in BBA
- Participated in 15 and won 11 titles in various intercollegiate events as Best Manager.
- Awarded as 'Best Student' in senior secondary school.

ACADEMIC PROJECT

You and Your Mind

https://youandyourmind.wixsite.com/website

February 2022

This is an academic project of developing a website and creating SEO-centric content related to a new business idea in a specific industry. You and Your mind is a platform (website) that provides a safe space for unspoken and ignored mental health issues.

QUOTE THAT I STAND FOR

It's not about being better than others, it's about being better than who you were yesterday.

ONE WORD I USE TO DESCRIBE MYSELF

"Driven"

I hereby declare that, the above mentioned information is true to best of my knowledge.